Tokimeki Falmeter Junction TV
Good Evening.
Rave reviews, sentiments.
Excuse me, my nose hurts.
I'm sorry, my nose hurts.
Today, I would like to play the sign-up game!
What's a sign-up? I'm sure you've never played the sign-up game.
I've never played the sign-up game.
Do I have to make myself taller? Something like that.
I don't know.
It's not like that.
It's just the rules.
We draw lots with the pentatonic pentatonic
With the pentatonic pentatonic as the theme.
Yes, sir.
For example, if it's Italy...
the word begins with the letter "i" and is smaller than the Italian word
and then increase the size from the person in front of you.
For example, if the subject is Italy
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
Stone, stone, stone, stone, stone, stone?
Stone, stone, stone, stone, stone, stone, stone
Stone is the smallest.
And then you make it bigger and bigger.
And if it gets bigger and bigger
the game is a success.
You know what I mean?
Julia has squid and stuff.
Yes, yes.
Chair. Squid. Chair.
Chair, parrot.
What? Why?
You're so tiny.
Dolphin. Dolphin?
Dolphin.
Dolphin, dolphin, dolphin.
So, we're gonna do this until we make it.
If we don't make it.
We can't go to rehearsal.
It's hard work.
So let's do our best to make it work.
Let's go to rehearsal.
We'll do our best.
Let's start with the subject
Tokyo Map Tour
I'd love to go.
I want to go!
Just looking at the words makes me want to go there!
I see.
That's the maximum
Order.
It doesn't have to be in order.
Is that okay?
Okay, here we go.
Wink.
It's all about order.
Well, maybe the first one's the easiest.
Yeah, I think so. First in line.
See?
Okay.
Wow, really?
Number two.
Number three.
Number four.
Number one.
Okay, okay.
I got it. I got it.
I live in Tokyo.
Tokyo is no good.
Tokyo's no good.
I have to come back to Tokyo to remember.
That's it?
That's it.
That?
When it starts with a sound.
I can't get the big one to come out.
I don't know what to do.
That one?
That's it.
What?
Oh, there it is.
It doesn't come up.
It's not coming out.
Guys, then.
Shaking time is 30 seconds.
Yes, sir.
All right, here we go.
Let's go.
What's that?
That's that little thing, isn't it?
What?
That little tiny thing.
Is it there?
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, I think it's too big.
But I don't know.
It's smaller than everyone else's.
I'm pretty tiny.
But I'm smaller than everyone else.
It's getting bigger and bigger, isn't it?
Oh, I don't know, maybe it's too subtle.
I don't know what to do.
That's all I got.
I don't know.
That one?
Is it really that one?
Huh?
I think it's too big.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wait, does this mean I'm big, or is this...
How big is this? I didn't draw anything that big.
Oh, wait a minute.
How big is that?
I don't know, I guess it's pretty big.
Oh, here.
It would be more interesting if you put them out in order with the piocas.
That's right.
I'll take them out in order with the Pioca.
Here we go.
Here comes the little one.
Ready?
Tomica!
Car girl
Tiny...
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good, isn't it?
Tiny.
Okay, here we go.
Tontoro.
Sad.
You should spread your wings.
Yeah, if you spread your wings.
Tundro.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It might be a long time.
Oh, no.Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Here we go.
Tontoro.
Oh, it's huge.
It's huge.
It's so big.
Very big
It's so big!
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't look at the screen.
It's too big.
It's huge.
A 10-kilogram Tontoro is probably pretty big.
Tontoro
Cara's Tontoro is huge!
It's huge!
Wait, sis.
It's been like 12 minutes.
Sis.
Hey, Aki-chan!
How do you like this?
No, I'm done
The end
It's over
What is your answer, Aki-chan?
Tom.
Which one?
Eh, eh, eh, eh
Crow
Crow.
Yeah, but, you know, like a human tom.
Tom
Big Tom
It's like I'm going to die.
Aki-chan is going to die.
Big Tom
Big Tom.
That's a big thing to say.
Not tiny.
Tiny
Tom.
Big Tom
Cat
Cats are surprisingly big
Yes, they are.
Tontoro might be big, too.
It might be big, right?
There they are.
They're all lined up.
You haven't seen them yet.
I've never seen them together.
I don't know.
They might be big.
But the live-action version is pretty much the same cat.
Oh, right.
The live-action version...
When I first saw it.
I thought it looked like a man's shoulder.
Yeah.
I was in English class or something.
You can tell by the look on his face.
Okay, let's take a look at the front.
Let's take a look.
Let's see.
This way.
A tiger.
Tigers, too.
And Totoro.
Totoro's big, too.
It's a good match.
Totoro's bigger.
That's a good match.
You mean Totoro's bigger?
Not bigger than Totoro.
That's great.
Hitori!
Look at that!
A lighthouse.
It's big!
What is it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Totoro or the lighthouse?
The lighthouse is bigger.
What's the question?
This way.
tanning alfresco music hall
Fire
Where we're playing
Where we're playing.
Fire.
Fire?
Hito-chan.
Hito-chan, let's use it like fire.
I can use it.
Seino
difficult
It's difficult
Difficult?
that means
You all read it in one sitting, right?
Good job!
Related
Hey, guys.
It's not too hard, is it?
It's hard.
This one's the best.
Is this possible?
Yes.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Yes, yes, yes.
Beautiful sound
Well then
I think we're good.
Okay, I'm going to pull it out from all of you.
I'm going to pull it out.
I'm gonna...
Knees.
Partial word production
Knee
Whose knee
Cabin's knee
The knee
The elbow
Elbow's
Knee of knee
I just raised an eyebrow.
You have a body part for a face.
Might work.
I think this could work.
I'm in.
Chickens!
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good
Chick chick chick
Knees.
Isn't that a little smaller than hers?
Her knees.
Chick chick.Chickens.
Chicks are big.
Chick's the longest term.
Knee bone
Chick.
The plate.
Could be a baby's knee.
Babies are small
Knee small
Small, small, small
The plate is pretty small.
Knees are big.
Big.
Next.
A shadow of a person
Pokemon
How big is it?
Maybe this much.
I can't imagine.
I guess it's okay then.
Let's continue.
It's bigger than a shadow of a tree.
Sunny.
I feel good
And I'm
HITO-chan
Is there Jerry?
Yuto's song?
But it's not a success.
Yuto's song.
It'll work, won't it?
It's fire.
Yes, it's fire.
What do you think?
What's the verdict?
Knees
What's there
Chick is small.
This one.
Not this one.
Not the chick.
I think they're about the same size.
It takes a knee to begin with.
I was pretty sure about this one.
That's a tough one.
It's hard.
One more time.
Let's see if I can finish this one.
I think I'm almost done.
Julia.
Julia, why don't you draw a question for us?
Here's a number.
Draw a number from there.
Next.
Let's do it.
That's good.
America.
No matter how big it is, it'll be fine.
It's good, it's good, it's big, it's big, it's big
Maybe there's a circle in 1.
It's hard
It's so hard!
Caking time
Let's get started.
It's really tiny
It's okay.
Anything is okay
It's okay if you get a bigger one
Oh, my God.
Isn't it smaller than the U.S.?
Okay, Julia.
I don't know what to do.
It's smaller than America.
It's not coming out.
She's not coming out.
It's smaller than America.
I don't think so.
It's not coming out.
Well, what's it like?
It's tiny.
It's pretty tiny.
But maybe...
Two tiny little things in one tiny little thing.
They'll say it's just like that.
You're pretty big and tall, Hiro-chan!
I see...
A tiny one?
Yes...
But not that tiny.
I asked for it.
Daddy, is that it?
Oh, here.
This one.
That one.
I wish it was only about 40,000 yen.
Oh, I don't know.
Okay, let's start with Kanami, please.
Ajinomoto grains
Certainly.
This is
You're good at this.
Particle level
This is good.
You think you can do it, Aki-chan?
Yes, America.
I'm feeling good now.
It's good.
Ice cream.
Oh, no, no, no.
Suddenly it gets really big!
Spring too!
Seino
Akichan
It looks good.
Looking good.
Here we go.
Seino
Akihabara
Let's go again.
One more time!
Okay.
Amazon River
It's smaller than America, isn't it?
Amazon River.
Which one is it?
I don't know.
Yes!
That's it!
That's good.
We made it.
We did it!
Give me that gulp.
Yes, sir.
What?
That's it?
That's it.the end
The end.
It's over.
Which way? This game...
Three times.
Three times and it worked.
Surprisingly fast
I could do all of them.
It was fun.
I enjoyed it.
I could do it.
I felt like I could do it.
That was fun.
Thank you all for watching.
Thank you very much.
See you next week.
See you next week!
Subscribe to our channel!
Subscribe to our channel